{
    "id": "03a101cb97a24feea947b407df1aeee8",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She devoted her life ………………….. helping the poor and the destitute.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "for",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "07a4e897e6ab4a5da1cab9aaa0e4a53a"
        },
        {
            "question": "Bad weather didn’t deter us ……………… starting our vacation.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "from",
                "for",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "299473b9e98649609632c927b085f5b2"
        },
        {
            "question": "Punishment is not necessarily a deterrent ……………….. crime.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f126017fa3be4f4899d6d7f717c96d0f"
        },
        {
            "question": "Be wary ………………… politicians who claim to be devoted public servants.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "off",
                "of",
                "about"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "06e087a14bbf4b6787e91456e51bd132"
        },
        {
            "question": "I despise anyone who is cruel ………………. animals.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "with",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8e3875d619f94ae3918bef3f43d8a9d2"
        },
        {
            "question": "We were desolated ……………….. the death of our good friend.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "by",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b977df18aacc4bc3a77e0f23d700f3c5"
        },
        {
            "question": "The desire ………………. fame drove him relentlessly.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "for",
                "by"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1947c301bfbf4de0bacbc3f0317897e8"
        },
        {
            "question": "Some animals can survive ...................... very little water.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "with",
                "by"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c846e4e35e584652a352704f9267a953"
        },
        {
            "question": "She was deprived …………………. her membership for nonpayment of dues.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "for",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "da4e35f2b3694e6aaa5513d7bee716db"
        },
        {
            "question": "I deposited 100 dollars ……………… my savings account.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "in",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "89ec3ca3016b4242835ad43c17e7197e"
        }
    ]
}